Nicolás Durango

Software Developer

Profile

Computer Engineer graduate from AUNAR, with a main focus on web development and API creation. My experience spans languages such as Python and JavaScript, and I have developed personal projects in various fields, from data analysis to full web applications. For the backend, I use frameworks like Django, while for the frontend, I prefer React/Vue.

I consider myself a proactive individual with a strong ability to adapt to new technologies and a constant commitment to improvement and continuous learning.

Employment History

Web Developer at ParqueSoft Meta, Villavicencio - Meta

August 2022 — October 2022

During my entrepreneurship internship assigned by the ParqueSoft Meta and Amazorinoquía organization, I played a key role in the development of a business web project. My responsibilities included:

- Backend development using the Django framework.
- · Database management with PostgreSQL.
- Web design and layout with CSS (using Bootstrap).
- JavaScript for animations and interactive features.
- · Version control through Git.

★ Featured Projects

FullStack Developer, Villavicencio - Meta

July 2023 - Present

I developed a web system for optimizing the order and inventory management of a restaurant, focusing on the following areas:

- Backend development using Django REST Framework and SQL database.
- Responsive interface design with React and Tailwind CSS.
- · Version control through Git.

Education

Computer Engineer, Corporación Universitaria Autónoma de Nariño, Villavicencio - Meta

February 2018 — June 2023

Details

Villavicencio - Meta Colombia +57 311 2815986 nikolasdurango@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn Github Portafolio

Skills

Git

Python

Django y DRF

Postman

JavaScript

React

Vue

Bootstrap

Tailwind CSS

Languages

Spanish (Native)

English (B1)